let questions =  [{
			"question": "In what year did Beethoven write the ninth symphony?",
			"option1": "1824",
			"option2": "1851",
			"option3": "1822",
			"option4": "1834",
			"answer": "1"			
		},

		{
			"question": "Which of this is not the subtitle of a Haydn symphony?",
			"option1": "Hornsignal",
			"option2": "Lamentatione",
			"option3": "Tragic",
			"option4": "Mercury",
			"answer": "3"	
		},

		{
			"question": "Which term among these is the odd one out?",
			"option1": "Aria",
			"option2": "Recitative",
			"option3": "Libretto",
			"option4": "Chorus",
			"answer": "3"	
		},

		{
			"question": "Where was Cellist Jaqueline du Pre born?",
			"option1": "Cheltenham",
			"option2": "Oxford",
			"option3": "Cambridge",
			"option4": "Cirencester",
			"answer": "2"
		},
		
		{
			"question": "What is Simon Rattle's middle name?",
			"option1": "Denis",
			"option2": "David",
			"option3": "Samuel",
			"option4": "Derek",
			"answer": "1"
		},
		
		{
			"question": "How many Ballades did Frederic Choping write?",
			"option1": "4",
			"option2": "12",
			"option3": "24",
			"option4": "48",
			"answer": "1"
		},
		
		{
			"question": "In which city was Mozart born?",
			"option1": "Paris",
			"option2": "Rome",
			"option3": "Vienna",
			"option4": "Salzburg",
			"answer": "4"
		},
		
		{
			"question": "Which other composer was born the same year as Handel?",
			"option1": "Bach",
			"option2": "Vivaldi",
			"option3": "Haydn",
			"option4": "Mozart",
			"answer": "1"
		},
		
		{
			"question": "What is Antonio Vivaldi most known for?",
			"option1": "Opera",
			"option2": "Inventing the Violin",
			"option3": "Concertos",
			"option4": "Theory teacher",
			"answer": "3"
		},
		
		{
			"question": "What was Antonio Vivaldi's middle name?",
			"option1": "Lucio",
			"option2": "Francesco",
			"option3": "Davide",
			"option4": "Ricardo",
			"answer": "1"
		}
];